Guide to the City Theatre Company Records, 1973-1993 CTC.1991.01
ULS Archives & Special Collections
- Additional Operational Files, 1979-1993; IV.
  - Comeback - Poster (Box 20, Folder 18)
  - Daytrips - Articles/Reviews, 1990-1991 (Box 20, Folder 19)
  - Development - Fiscal year, 1993 (Box 20, Folder 20)
  - Development Gala - Season, 1991-1992 (Box 20, Folder 21)
  - Dracula - Poster (Box 20, Folder 22)
  - Evelyn The Polka King, 1992-1993 (Box 20, Folder 23-25)
  - Financial reports - Season, 1992-1993 (Box 20, Folder 26)
  - Frankie Johnny in the Claire de Lune, Reviews/Articles, 1988-1989 (Box 20, Folder 27)
  - Hartwood - Reviews/Articles, 1989-1990 (Box 20, Folder 28-29)
  - Holiday Memories, 1992-1993 (Box 20, Folder 30-32)
  - Illusions of Fantasy Mime Troupe - Poster (Box 20, Folder 33)
  - Le Bourgeois Avant Garde, 1990-1991 (Box 21, Folder 1)
  - Man Who Lived Underground (Box 21, Folder 2)
  - Maybe I'm Doing it Wrong, 1984-1985 (Box 21, Folder 3)
  - Miss Ever's Boys, 1991-1992 (Box 21, Folder 4-7)
  - NAMES Project Display - Articles (see also Baltimore Waltz) (Box 21, Folder 8-9)
  - Newspaper clippings, 1979-1988 (Box 21, Folder 10)
  - Our Country's Good, 1991-1992 (Box 21, Folder 11-13)
  - Painting It Red, 1988-1989 (Box 21, Folder 14)
  - Playworks articles, 1989 (Box 21, Folder 15)
  - Press releases, 1979-1988 (Box 21, Folder 16-17)
  - Production history - 1980 through 1993 (Box 21, Folder 18)
  - Publicity book, 1987-1988 (Box 21, Folder 19-22)
  - Real Inspector Hound - Poster, 1977 (Box 21, Folder 23)
  - Road to Mecca - Articles/Reviews, 1991 (Box 21, Folder 24)
  - Season 1979 - Poster (Box 21, Folder 25)
  - Season 14-18, 1987-1992 (Box 21, Folder 26-30)
  - Steel Kiss - Articles/Reviews, 1990-1991 (Box 22, Folder 1)
  - Subscription ads (Box 22, Folder 2)
  - Talk of the City newsletter, 1989-1992 (Box 22, Folder 3)
  - Talk Radio - Articles/Reviews, 1988-1989 (Box 22, Folder 4)
  - Tamer of Horses - Articles/Reviews, 1987-1988 (Box 22, Folder 5)
  - Temptation - Articles/Reviews, 1992-1993 (Box 22, Folder 6-8)
  - Theatre Sports - Articles/Reviews, 1991 (Box 22, Folder 9)
  - Tuesday/Act Without Words, 1991-1992 (Box 22, Folder 10-12)
  - Unidentified Photos (Box 22, Folder 13)
  - Voice of the Prairie - Articles/Reviews, 1988-1989 (Box 22, Folder 14)
  - Waiting for Lefty - Poster (Box 22, Folder 15)
  - Wings - Poster (Box 22, Folder 16)
- Oversized Materials, 1979-1988; V.
  This series is for all oversized materials in the collection. It contains posters, production scores, and floor plans. The materials are arranged alphabetical order.
  - American Buffalo - Poster (Box 23, Folder 1)
  - Blues in the Night and True West at Hartwood Acres - Poster (Box 23, Folder 2)
  - Bouquet Street Theatre - Floor Plan (Box 23, Folder 3)
  - Bricklayers - Poster (Box 23, Folder 4)
  - Cabaret Verboten - Poster (Box 23, Folder 5)
  - Carnegie Institute Lecture Hall Floor Plan (Box 23, Folder 6)
  - Cole/T Bone n Weasel at Hartwood Acres - Poster (Box 23, Folder 7)
  - Colored Museum - Poster (Box 23, Folder 8)
  - Crimes of the Heart - Poster (Box 23, Folder 9)
  - Curse of the Starving Class - Poster (Box 23, Folder 10)
  - Danube/Ohio Impromptu and Catastrophe - Poster (Box 23, Folder 11)
  - Day of the Picnic - Poster (Box 23, Folder 12)
  - Daytrips - Poster (Box 23, Folder 13)
  - Fool for Love - Poster (Box 23, Folder 14)
  - Frankie and Johnny in the Claire de Lune - Poster (Box 23, Folder 15)
  - Glengarry Glen Ross - Poster (Box 23, Folder 16)
  - Hypochondriac - Poster (Box 23, Folder 17)
  - Incommunicado - Poster (Box 23, Folder 18)
  - Indians - Set Design Floor Plan, 1981-1982 (Box 23, Folder 19)
  - Josephine the Mouse Singer - Poster (Box 23, Folder 20)
  - Loose Ends - Poster (Box 23, Folder 21)
  - Maybe I'm Doing it Wrong - Poster (Box 23, Folder 22)
  - Miss Evers' Boys (Box 23, Folder 23)
  - My Queer Body [Tim Miller] - Poster (Box 23, Folder 24)
  - Our Country's Good - Poster (Box 23, Folder 25)
  - Painting It Red - Poster (Box 23, Folder 26)
  - Perfect Party - Poster (Box 23, Folder 27)
  - Principia Scriptoriae - Set Design Floor Plan, 1987-1988 (Box 23, Folder 28)
  - Road to Mecca - Poster (Box 23, Folder 29)
  - 70 Scenes from Halloween - Poster (Box 23, Folder 30)
  - Sexual Perversity in Chicago - Poster (Box 23, Folder 31)
  - Steel City - Poster (Box 23, Folder 32)
  - Steel Kiss - Poster (Box 23, Folder 33)
  - Talk Radio - Poster (Box 23, Folder 34)
  - Talking with... - Poster (Box 23, Folder 35)
  - Tamer of Horses - Set Design Floor Plan, 1987-1988 (Box 23, Folder 36)
  - Theatre Sports at Hartwood Acres - Poster (Box 23, Folder 37)
  - Tuesday/Act without Words - Poster (Box 23, Folder 38)
  - Voice of the Prairie - Poster (Box 23, Folder 39)
  - Working - Poster and Score (Box 23, Folder 40)
  - Maekaill, Dorothy (sp?) - Signed photograph Curtis, Misc.(flat shelving) (Oversize 10)
  - Accounting for Love - Poster Curtis, Misc.(flat shelving) (Oversize 11)